21 Willow St. East Kingston, NS B0P 1R0

nwtaylor04@gmail.com

(902)-804-1666

# **Objective**

My goals overall are to become a more social person, learn how to communicate with people better and develop my own programming skills, whether it be by learning from other people or learning on my own through trial and error. When it comes to programming I am very persistent on getting it right the first time I do it, and if I don't, it is a learning experience and I take it all at face value.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Babysitter - 2016 - 2020

Experience in caring for children ages 18 months and up

Lawn/Yardworker - 2016 - 2022

Mowing, cleaning up garbage and waste from animals, grass trimming, wood piling, shoveling driveways

Strawberry Picker - July 2019

Picked strawberries at a local farm

Wal-Mart Fulfillment Worker - September 2020 - October 2022

Stocking shelves, cleaning up spills/dropped items, facing shelves, moving heavy items, etc...

Wal-Mart Cashier - July 2022 - August 2022 (Leave of Absence as of August 20th)

Assisted customers at self checkout as well as served customers at tills

### **EDUCATION**

Completed grade 10 at West Kings District High School with Honours with Distinction

Completed grade 11 at West Kings District High School with Honours

Completed grade 12 at West Kings District High School with Honours and received High School Diploma

Current student at NSCC COGS (2022-2024)

#### **VOLUNTEER WORK AND INTERESTS**

Myth or History TV show - Crew Assistant - 2019 - 2020

Set up equipment, video recording, sound setup and recording, assist with drone usage, help crew investigate

West Kings Student Council - Grad Rep - 2021-2022

Representing the graduating class, helping plan events with others, spirit days

Football Player - 2018 - 2020

Wide Receiver for West Kings Football Team

Beginner Programmer (IT Programming at COGS)

Learning different languages, currently know Python, HTML5 and CSS, as well as some Java

## **REFERENCES**

Available upon request